

# **Taylor Stimbert**

Product Designer

### **Details**

Address

San Francisco, California

Phone

(315) 802-8179

**Email** 

tstimbert@gmail.com

### Skills

**Figma** 



Sketch



Adobe Photoshop



Adobe Illustrator



Principle



Adobe XD



### Certifications

## **Objective**

I'm a product designer focused on ensuring great user experience and meeting business needs of designed products. I'm also experienced in implementing marketing strategies and developing both on and offline campaigns. My philosophy is to make products understandable, useful and long-lasting at the same time recognizing they're never finished and constantly changing. I'm always excited to face new challenges and problems.

## **Experience**

#### Uber

**Product Designer** 

Mar 2015 - Present

- Designed safety-focused experiences for Riders and Drivers
- Physical space problem solving and it's interaction with the digital
- Navigated organization to achieve operational improvements

#### **IFTTT**

**Product Designer** 

Dec 2013 - Mar 2015

- Designed safety-focused experiences for Riders and Drivers
- Physical space problem solving and it's interaction with the digital
- Navigated organization to achieve operational improvements

### **Google Maps**

**Product Designer** 

June 2012 - Sep 2013

- Designed safety-focused experiences for Riders and Drivers
- Physical space problem solving and it's interaction with the digital

Google UX Design
Certificate

Navigated organization to achieve operational improvements

# **Education**

# **Brown University**

Interdisciplinary studies, Sep 2010 - May 2013

# Language

English ★★★★

Italian ★★★★